thephonesupport.com 2017-12-25

# Privacy Policy - The Phone Support

  * **NOTICE** When we ask for your personal information, we will tell you why we need it and what we will do with it.
  * **CHOICE** When we contact you for marketing purposes, we will let you know how to remove your name from future marketing efforts.
  * **SECURITY** We will use reasonable security measures to protect the personal information we receive from you.
  * **SHARING** We will never share your personal information with any affiliates. If so is done it will be done only with your prior permission.

## "THE PHONE SUPPORT" PRIVACY POLICY

The following Privacy Policy describes the information and privacy practices for "The Phone Support" where your personal information is collected by, or on behalf of, "The Phone Support". When you provide us your personal information, you consent to the information practices described in this policy.

## INFORMATION COLLECTED BY "THE PHONE SUPPORT"

As part of your interaction with "The Phone Support", we may collect personal information such as:

  * Contact information, including name, mailing address, phone number and e-mail address
  * Purchase information, billing and/or shipping information.
  * Product information, including services, devices and software used.

## As a Registered customer of "The Phone Support Pvt. Ltd." We might call you for the following specific reasons:

  1. Follow up calls for troubleshooting issues.
  2. Regular Maintenance calls
  3. Customer service/Feedback Calls.
  4. Subscription Status / Renewal Calls.
  5. Follow up calls for processing refunds etc.

## USES OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use the personal information you provide for purposes including, but not limited to:

  * Fulfilling requests for products, services or information
  * Tracking and confirming online orders
  * Delivering or installing products
  * Providing customer services
  * Satisfaction Surveys
  * Improving the effectiveness & quality of our Web sites, our marketing endeavors and our services offered
  * Conducting research and analysis

## SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

"The Phone Support" does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties.  
We also display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at support@thephonesupport.com

## CHOICES REGARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

"The Phone Support" communicates with our customers through multiple channels to enhance customer experience content and new products or services. Once you provide your personal information, we may contact you through direct mail, e-mail or phone. We may continue to communicate with you through these channels unless you request to stop receiving these communications by opting out.  
If you send an e-mail or call us, please be sure to include your full name, address, phone number and e-mail address, as well as the specific changes you would like to make. This will ensure we correctly identify you in our systems and accurately process your request.  
"The Phone Support" will take the appropriate steps to modify your preferences with respect to our communications. Due to production, mailing and system timelines, it may take some time to process your request. The following guidelines are provided for your convenience:

  * 10 business days for e-mails, direct mail and phone

Until your requested change takes effect, you may still receive communications from us.

## UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

"The Phone Support" wants your personal information to be accurate and complete. We provide several different methods for you to update your personal information.

To update your name, address, phone number and/or e-mail information:

  * **** You may call the number given at the [www.thephonesupport.com](http://www.thephonesupport.com/) website.
  * Send a request to: [support@thephonesupport.com](mailto:support@thephonesupport.com)

If you send an e-mail or call us, please be sure to include your current information and the requested changes. We will respond to your request ASAP.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## REMOTE ACCESS

"The Phone Support" offers remote access service to assist in diagnosing and resolving system issues. This process allows a "The Phone Support" Agent to remotely access your computer to determine the problem and either repair it or provide advice on what options are available to fix the issue. By taking advantage of this service, you are giving permission to a "The Phone Support" Agent to log into your computer which may contain personal information. A "The Phone Support" Agent will only search your computer to determine the cause of the problem and will attempt to limit their interaction with your files to a minimum. It is your responsibility to ensure all of your files, especially those containing personal information, are secure to prevent any type of data loss or corruption.

## CONCERNS ABOUT THE PRIVACY OR SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Please contact "The Phone Support" to report a known or suspected privacy or security breach or to submit privacy or security-related questions or complaints. After receiving your inquiry, we will respond within five business days. You may contact us in the following ways:

  * ****The telephone number provided at the[www.thephonesupport.com](http://www.thephonesupport.com/) website.
  * Send a communication to: [support@thephonesupport.com](mailto:support@thephonesupport.com)

## PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

We may need to update our Privacy Policy as "The Phone Support" and our customers grow and evolve. If we make any material changes, including any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective, as well as inform you of any choices you may have with respect to these changes. "The Phone Support" reserves the right to make changes to this policy as & when required.

## CONTACT IINFORMATION

Should you have further queries, please e-mail us at support@thephonesupport.com or you can drop a mail at:

##  The Phone Support

Should you have further queries, please e-mail us at support@thephonesupport.com or you can drop a mail at:

 **The Phone Support**  
572 & 573, G-2, Tower B-1 Evolve,  
T/ITeS Mahindra World City,  
Village Kalwara, Taluka Sanganer,  
Jaipur- 302037,  
INDIA
